[{"answer": "We're learning the latest from a source that's close to the death investigation, Piers.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 33, "question": "Don, what's the latest tonight?", "qSentId": 32}, {"answer": "EMON: Yes.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 56, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 55}, {"answer": "Well, I was in California.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 94, "question": "How did you feel when you heard that Whitney had died, I mean, given everything we know about her lifestyle in the last few years?", "qSentId": 93}, {"answer": "Very.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "I just wonder how shocking it was to people that ho knew her well?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "Look, I think it's not just papers, it's magazines, it's television networks, I mean CNN like everybody else has been doing a lot of coverage of this.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "What is it?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "I have.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Have you spoken to any of the family?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "Well, I'm -- all I'm saying is we don't know.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "Do you think it's as simple as that?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, I think Whitney Houston came from the church.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Do the fans have a right to be part of this or do you think it was the sensible thing to do?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 178, "question": "Very sadly died last -- six months ago?", "qSentId": 177}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 180, "question": "And 46 years, I think, I've read that you wrote together, is that right?", "qSentId": 179}, {"answer": "Absolutely.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 228, "question": "Do you think it's the right thing to do?", "qSentId": 227}, {"answer": "You're in dangerous territory now because the song was actually written for Chaka Khan.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "When you -- when you wrote, \"I'm Every Woman,\" and then you heard her sing it, has there ever been any singer that you've ever heard who could have sung it better than Whitney Houston?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "I think she will be -- you know, it's interesting.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "How would you think that she would like her legacy to be in terms of the music?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "By pure chance.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 278, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 277}, {"answer": "Well, it was a very -- I can appreciate Chaka's feelings and I respect that.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 290, "question": "Was it a hard decision and when you got there what was it actually like in the room?", "qSentId": 289}, {"answer": "I will remember a young woman who always had a bright smile, brought joy to my life.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 303, "question": "How will you remember?", "qSentId": 302}, {"answer": "That was a while ago.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What do you mean, like trashing me in front of, like, 200 million people at the Golden Globes?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "You like jokes?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "That's followed me around.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 352, "question": "Isn't it?", "qSentId": 351}, {"answer": "Well, because for a very long time you would never have imagined being in Hollywood.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "I was going to ask why you ask me?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know about that.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "What is the reality of Hollywood excess, the type that we've seen that caused the death of Whitney Houston?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 379, "question": "Is it to not be famous too early?", "qSentId": 378}, {"answer": "Well, I think so.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 385, "question": "Is it a lot easier, is my point, to be older and become famous?", "qSentId": 384}, {"answer": "What I can't believe is the way you look, because we all fell in love back in Britain with fat, chubby Ricky.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 393, "question": "It's the I can't believe my luck that I get up in the morning, have an idea, and I can start writing that idea and it will get made at the moment, you know?", "qSentId": 392}, {"answer": "No, I didn't.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 400, "question": "You didn't tell me then, though, did you?", "qSentId": 399}, {"answer": "Not much at all.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 413, "question": "How much weight have you lost?", "qSentId": 412}, {"answer": "I got some free -- those things in a luxury lounge once, those -- I thought those made me gag.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 428, "question": "Hollywood smiling?", "qSentId": 427}, {"answer": "It wasn't a vanity kick.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 440, "question": "What made you go on this vanity kick?", "qSentId": 439}, {"answer": "-- \"The death of a fight-useless chubby loser with -- who never cleans his teeth and stinks.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "Where would you be without that?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "I don't -- never got groupies.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 475, "question": "Do you get more groupies now?", "qSentId": 474}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 477, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 476}, {"answer": "ERVAIS: I --", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 484, "question": "A svelte comedic auteur or as a chubby loser?", "qSentId": 483}, {"answer": "\"Seinfeld,\" lovely show.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "History of television?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 566, "question": "You love Twitter, don't you?", "qSentId": 565}, {"answer": "I like it for lots of reasons.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 568, "question": "Why do you like it so much?", "qSentId": 567}, {"answer": "Well, you know, as a comedian --", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "What were you getting at?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "Well, I thought I looked intellectual there --", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "-- you'd fit in well looking like that?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 597, "question": "Always?", "qSentId": 596}, {"answer": "Well, but they shouldn't.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 606, "question": "How does your -- how does your atheism, which you're passionate about -- how does that play with your American audience, given that so many people in America are God-fearing people, and probably take exception to it?", "qSentId": 605}, {"answer": "I don't think so.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Do I do that?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "Yes, please.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Should we play you what Steve Carell said about you?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Oh, not in a million years, no.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 711, "question": "Could you do what Ricky does?", "qSentId": 710}, {"answer": "I think I would just get too skittish.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 713, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 712}, {"answer": "Perhaps, but to actually go in front of people and --", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 716, "question": "But you could play a Ricky Gervais character?", "qSentId": 715}, {"answer": "That's right.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 730, "question": "ORGAN: -- you're all heart, aren't you?", "qSentId": 729}, {"answer": "He's great.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "Do you like Steve Carrell?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "I'm assuming women.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "What, with -- romantic love?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Once.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 781, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 780}, {"answer": "Well, we are, really.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 792, "question": "Why haven't you married her yet?", "qSentId": 791}, {"answer": "Oh, I'd never say never.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 797, "question": "Do you think you ever will?", "qSentId": 796}, {"answer": "ERVAIS: I don't know.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 805, "question": "How do you show your romantic side?", "qSentId": 804}, {"answer": "There's loads of things whizzing through my head, but they're all from childhood.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 825, "question": "It would be professional, really -- a moment in your life, what would it be?", "qSentId": 824}, {"answer": "I just remembered one.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "Like what?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Thank God.", "docId": "120216pmt", "aSentId": 865, "question": "There is only one Ricky Gervais?", "qSentId": 864}]